[{"answer": "Well, it's a difficult situation over there because the alternative to not knowing was knowing which would have been another headache.", "docId": "140108pmt", "aSentId": 32, "question": "Is there some surprise that he hasn't already taken action and fired those responsible?", "qSentId": 31}, {"answer": "That he's appalled.", "docId": "140108pmt", "aSentId": 39, "question": "Mr. Mayor, what is your reaction to Chris Christie's statement late this afternoon?", "qSentId": 38}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "140108pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "Do you believe that Chris Christie knew nothing about this as he claims?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "I would agree, you know.", "docId": "140108pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "It's hard to imagine a more serious abuse of power, isn't it Mr. Mayor?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "OKOLICH: People that are in these positions of authority that behave this way, that put petty politics ahead of the health safety and welfare of my residents and the residents of the entire state of New Jersey truly can't be in those positions.", "docId": "140108pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "Should people be fired, should any of any of these people be in a job by tomorrow morning one to be name in shame today?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "No, zero.", "docId": "140108pmt", "aSentId": 126, "question": "Have you heard from anybody in Chris Christie's camp including the governor's staff?", "qSentId": 125}, {"answer": "Remain mindful, Piers, I'm not on his radar, so I trust, I'm not in his (inaudible) either.", "docId": "140108pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "No apology?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "Well, I have been involved in this issue for four months which Mayor Sokolich knows.", "docId": "140108pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "What is your reaction to this extraordinary development today which lays clear evidence now that takes right to the heart of Chris Christie's operation that they did this deliberately?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "140108pmt", "aSentId": 154, "question": "-- if I could jump in, should Chris Christie be firing people over this?", "qSentId": 153}, {"answer": "Well, if you call the traffic study three or four days beforehand where you have the idea put forward that you're going to close a few lanes and look at that, I suppose you vaguely could call that a traffic study.", "docId": "140108pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "Is it likely that that was ever in their minds?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "Yeah, as you're talking, John, we're actually looking pictures from the time back in September where you can see the traffic currents (ph) and everything else.", "docId": "140108pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "It was over 30 years that's been done that way, you know, why not continue?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "It's very serious I think it could threaten his presidential ambitions if he is directly tied to this scandal which he hasn't yet been.", "docId": "140108pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "How serious could this be for Chris Christie?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "I don't like or just like it, it's just kind of what it is.", "docId": "140108pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "Do you like the fact that you have this slightly intimidating reputation?", "qSentId": 245}]